our.com 2018-04-04

# Privacy Policy - Our.com

### Data Protection and Privacy Policy

THE NETWIZZY COMPANY, SL, (herein, THE NETWIZZY COMPANY) is a registered company whose head office is located in Valencia, Spain on Calle Daniel Balaciart 2, mezzanine, postcode 46020 with the contact email address legal@our.com.

NETWIZZY THE COMPANY is duly registered in the Mercantile Registry of Valencia, Spain Volume 8497, Book 5787, Folio 212, Section 8, Page V-115519, 1st entry. C.I.F number is B97726913.

The operator is authorized to store and analyze connection data, especially IP source and destination data and all other access data, to protect the computer itself and those of third parties. The operator is authorized, and the user grants their consent with registration as well as to the processing of usage statistics, provided that they are not specific to any individuals.

Concerning the treatment of user data, the operator shall comply with the relevant legal provisions for data protection. The data will be processed by an automated security system. In case of abuse, we reserve the right to pass this information on to the competent authorities in the event of a corresponding legal necessity.

In compliance with the provisions of Law 15/1999 on December 13, Protection of Personal Data, and regulations, THE NETWIZZY COMPANY hereby informs that any communication through the website, as well as the registration and participation in our games, will entail the processing of confidential personal information of the sender, which will be incorporated into a file owned by THE NETWIZZY COMPANY. The collection and processing of this personal data aims to maintain its relationship with THE NETWIZZY COMPANY, sending users information about the activities, products and services of THE NETWIZZY COMPANY.

Please note that THE NETWIZZY COMPANY has adopted adequate levels of security for the data provided, and has also installed all the resources as well as technical and organizational measures at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and/or theft of the data provided.

Also, please note that you can contact THE NETWIZZY COMPANY at any time to exercise your right to access your data, or for the rectification or opposition to the use of your data thereof, or cancellation, by sending a written communication and enclosing a copy of your ID or official document attesting your identity to THE NETWIZZY COMPANY, in Valencia, Spain on Calle Daniel Balaciart 2, mezzanine, postcode 46020 or by sending an email to THE NETWIZZY COMPANY at: legal@our.com, attaching a copy of your valid ID, national identity card or any other documentation that identifies you.

The company is committed to treating your data confidentially, the computers that store personal data follow the provisions of Royal Decree 1720/2007 in Spain, approving the Regulations implemented by law for the protection of personal data.

The User expressly agrees that THE NETWIZZY COMPANY can transfer your personal data being processed to any company that has signed a partnership agreement in writing with THE NEtWIZZY COMPANY.

The services offered by THE NETWIZZY COMPANY on its Website are not intended for users under 14.

The operator shall take all possible technical measures to protect user data in its possession but nevertheless will not respond nor is responsible in the event that third parties, using illegal procedures, take and use the data for other purposes. The claim for damages by the user or third parties against the operator on such grounds is expressly excluded by agreement.

We allow you to register with us through Facebook Connect or other SNS verification options in creating an account or profile within the Service. We may also provide a more common way to register, in which we ask you to provide the following information: your age or date of birth (for age control and/or to better understand who our users are), your name and surname; your email address, a password and other information to help us confirm that you are the person accessing the account.

We have taken technical and organizational measures necessary to ensure that both our internal and external partners comply with the instructions on data protection.

We inform you that we collect personal information: 

  * that you enter when registering on our website or in one of our games.
  * that you enter in order to make an inquiry.
  * that you enter in order to use and pay for services and payment services.
  * that you enter when you voluntarily want to participate in surveys or advertising campaigns, or to receive newsletters.

We collect remote usage data to the extent that it is necessary for the performance of services or for the payment of them. This data includes, in particular, processes and states of the game, as well as information regarding the purchase and payment of services.

### Information We Receive or Collect When You Access Our.com Games from a Mobile Device

If you play games from THE NETWIZZY COMPANY on your mobile phone or other mobile devices, including iPads and tablets, we collect your unique mobile device identifier, including MAC address and IP address. In certain games we create and assign your device an identifier similar to an account number. We may collect the name you have associated with your device, type of device, your phone number, country and other information you choose to provide, such as user name, character name, geographic location or email address. We may also access your contacts to let you invite friends to join you on the Service.

### Payment information

If you buy directly from THE NETWIZZY COMPANY, a license to use money or virtual in-game content, we collect the billing information and financial information necessary to process your charges, which may include your mailing and email address. THE NETWIZZY COMPANY may also receive the billing and payment information that you provide when your purchase is processed by a third party.

We collect your information in order to fulfill our contract with you. It is especially important to properly process payment orders made by you, as well as monitor compliance with the conditions of use and game rules.

### Cookies

For technical purposes and to make our Internet experience as enjoyable as possible, we use, like many other companies do, so-called Cookies. These cookies are normally deleted automatically from your hard drive when you leave our website. Some cookies may be stored however for technical reasons on your hard drive for a longer period of time. Your browser may be set so that cookies are rejected as a general rule, or to be deleted in individual cases. The User decides whether to accept or delete cookies set by that web browser. If you do not want cookies to be stored or want to erase some in particular, you should follow the instructions on how to do so from the developer of the browser. The use of our websites may be restricted wholly or partly for technical reasons as a result of the aforementioned cookies.

Cookies collect information about the games and the frequency the user plays them (for example, at what time of day, day of week). They also collect information about the time period in which you use the website and each of the games. In addition, demographic information is saved as well as the age and gender of the user. The operator will enter, examine and use the information collected by cookies both to adapt the website to the behavior, needs and interests of the respective user, and generate statistics and create user groups. The information provided by cookies will also be used to allow certain third parties to display advertisements on the website. Additionally, the information collected in relation to the user's browsing habits will be updated and constantly expanding.

The user expressly agrees to the use of cookies and retargeting cookies by the operator. Furthermore, the user explicitly agrees to the automatic treatment (eg, through cookies) of data that you have provided about yourself and that the operator has collected.

### Data collection for statistical purposes

Concerning statistical evaluation, we perform partial reports on our Internet deals from which we collected data, such as operating system version, browser and version, IP address and other system data. This data is used for statistical evaluation in order to adjust our Internet offers to the user needs. Whenever possible the data will be anonymous.

### Revocation of consent

You are free to withdraw your consent to data processing. To unsubscribe from the newsletter or other emails, you should follow the instructions therein. There will be no additional expense to your basic rates. For other revocation of consents please contact the support service of the pages corresponding to the games used. In case of cancellation, there will not be additional costs that do not correspond to your basic rate.
